Pranav Devkar

Software Developer

Experienced Front-End Developer skilled in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, NextJS, Laravel and JavaScript. Good at making responsive and user-friendly websites. Works well with teams to complete projects on time. Always learning the latest web trends and best practices.

devpranavdevkar@gmail.com

917385131197

Pune

in linkedin.com/in/devpranavdevkar

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Bizionic Tecnology Pvt Ltd

06/2024 - Present

Hydrabad

Frontend Developer

Neuromonk Infotech Pvt. Ltd.

07/2022 - 06/2024

Pune

Intern Frontend Developer

Neuromonk Infotech Pvt. Ltd.

01/2022 - 06/2022

Pune

PROJECTS

InstaHirin 🗹

Bizionictech Website 🗷

Vidyasagar Academy 🗷

Arramton 🗷

B4-School (USA) Z

The Institute of chartered Accountants of India 🗷

Ski and Snowboard India (SSI)

Jai Ganesh Industries 🗹

Spright Software Systems

E&A Enterprises LLC 🗷

The CCID 🗷

Vved Veg Restaurant 🗷

Mutha & Rathod Timber Industries LLP 2

SKILLS

IL CSS Bootstra

ACHIEVEMENTS

Appreciation Certificate From Neuromonk Infotech

CERTIFICATES

Certificate Name

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Movies

Songs

Codeing

EDUCATION

MCA

JSPM's Rajarshi Shahu College Of Engneering

08/2019 - 05/2022

Pune

BCA

Yashwantrao Chavan College, Urun Islampur

07/2016 - 05/2019

Urun-Islampur